Preliminary Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Records, 1920s-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2008-0270), 1920s-2005 and undated, (449 boxes)
  - Individuals' Papers
    - Anthony Rau (Box 340A)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 346)
    - Brian Roberts-Wray (see also Kodak account files) (Box 335)
    - Brian Roberts-Wray (Box 348)
    - Allen Thomas (Box 246)
  - Knowledge Centre
    - Card index, IPA papers, miscellaneous publications (Box 369)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 178.6 Alcohol Use (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 312.5 Marriage (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 323.3 Social Classes (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 325.1 Immigration and Immigrants (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 325.2 Emigration (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 940.06(E) Europe Advertising/Marketing/Media (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 940.06(H) Europe/EEC Consumer Products (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: Subject Index (Box 385)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 330.941 Recession (Box 366)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 330.943 Economic--General (Box 366)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 385 Railways (Box 366)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 929.74 Awards--General (Box 366)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 929.742 Supermarketing Awards (Box 366)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 330.944 Millennium (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 331.4 Employment of Women (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 331.41 Women--Sex Equality (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 339.49 Conservation and Recycling (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 339.491 Conservation (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 389.2 Metrication (conversion to metric system) (Box 319)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 380.1622 Nationalized Industries (Box 328)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 380.1623 Privatisation and Nationalisation (Box 328)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 383.3 Telecommunications (Box 328)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 383.4 Telephones (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 383.5 Telephone Selling (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 621.3841 Radio (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 621.3846 BBC (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 621.3847 BBC Attitudes to Advertising (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 621.3848 Reith Lectures (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 621.3882 Television Broadcasting (Box 261)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 610 Medicine--General (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 610.69 Doctors and Nurses (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 612.39 Nutrition--General (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 612.399 Vitamins (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 612.65 Height and Weight (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 613.24 Slimming Diets (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 613.4 Baths and Bathing (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 613.78 Sleep (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614 Public Health (Box 318)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614.2 National Health Service (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614.200 Private Health Insurance (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614.202 Mental Health (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614.3 Food Hygiene and Food Poisoning (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 614.7 Pollution (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 615.783 Aspirin etc. (Box 329)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.2 Motor Industry (Box 310)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.21 Motor Industry Statistics (Box 310)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.22 Car Parts (Box 310)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.222 Motor Cars (Box 310)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.2221 Taxicabs (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.223 Trucks (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.2275 Motorcycles (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.2486 Tires (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.25 Internal Combustion Engines (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.27 Car Accessories (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.281 Motoring (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.282 Motor Racing (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.283 Car Hire (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 629.285 Garages (Box 330)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 615 Drugs (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 637 Dairy Products (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 639.2 Fish and Fishing Industry (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 641 Cooking (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 641.36 Meat (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 641.38 Sausages (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 641.83 Salads (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 642.11 Breakfasts (Box 371)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 633.33 Peanuts/Nuts (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 633.34 Soya Beans (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 633.35 Artificial Sweeteners (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 633.6 Sugar (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 634 Fruit (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 634.11 Apples (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 635 Vegetables (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 635.21 Potatoes (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 636.4132 Pork and Bacon (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 636.5 Poultry and Poultry Foods (Box 308)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643 Home--Bathroom (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2 Domestic Appliances (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.24 Electrical Appliances (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.241 White Goods (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2411 Cookers (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2412 Dishwashers (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2413 Refrigerators/Freezers (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2414 Vacuum Cleaners (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.242 Small Electrical Appliances (Box 331)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.2421 Food Mixers (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.3 Cookware (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.31 Kitchens and Kitchen Furniture (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.32 Kitchen Utensils (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 643.33 Kitchen Wraps (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 644.1 Central/Domestic Heating (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 644.3 Domestic Lighting (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 647.9 Catering (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 647.94 Hotels (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 647.941 Inns and Public Houses (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 647.95 Eating Out (Box 257)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 648.1 Washing (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 648.18 Launderettes (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 648.24 Washing Machines (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8713 Furniture Retailing (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.872 Department Stores (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.873 Co-Operative Societies (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.874 Chain Stores (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.875 Independent Retailers (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8751 Grocery Trade (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8756 Chemists (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8765 Self-Service (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8766 Discount Stores (Box 303)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8 Marketing (Box 306)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.813 Export Marketing (Box 306)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.816 Capital Goods Market (Box 306)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.8177 Luxury Goods Market (Box 306)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.82 Sales Management (Box 306)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.877 Automatic Vending Machines (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.878 Mobile Shops and Street Vendors (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.879 Shopping Centers (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.883 Hire Purchase (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 658.884 Mail Order (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659 Advertising--General (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.00037 Advertising Law (Box 309)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.00037 Advertising Law (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.002 Advertising Expenditure (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.003 Economic Effects of Advertising (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.013 Criticism of Advertising (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.015 Psychology of Advertising (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.0157 Subliminal Advertising (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.062 Advertising Associations and Clubs (Box 378)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.068 Advertising Ethics (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.068 Advertising Standard Authority (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.0682 Codes of Advertising Practice (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.069 Advertising Careers (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.07 Advertising Education (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.11 Public Relations (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.1121 Company Reports (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.1122 Financial Services Advertising (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.14 Sponsorship (Box 151)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.14 Sponsorship (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.21 Government Advertising and Public Relations (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.211 Central Office of Information (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.22 Corporate Image (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.235 Classified Advertising (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.24 Co-operative Advertising (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.25 Technical and Industrial Advertising (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.3 Advertising Agencies--General (Box 2)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.3 Advertising Agencies--General (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Backer Spielvogel Bates (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 CIA Media (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Grey Advertising (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Leo Burnett (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Lowe Howard Spink (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 McCann-Erickson (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Olgivy & Mather (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Publicis (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.3051 D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB), Benton & Bowles (Box 379)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.3051 Saatchi/Cordiant (Box 379A)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Saatchi & Saatchi (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Ted Bates (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 WCRS (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.305 Young & Rubicam (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.306 Media Independents (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.31 Choosing an Agency (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.32 Client-Agency Relations (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.33 Agency Administration (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.332 Agency Staff (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.333 Account Planning (Box 321)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.334 Agency Accounting (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.3344 Agency Billings (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.41 Agency Solicitation (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.44 Advertising-Sales Ratio (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.5 Advertising--Creative Aspects (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.51 Advertising--Music and Jingles (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.513 Humor in Advertising (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.5135 Cartoons (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.53 Copy Writing and Copywriters (Box 208)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.43 Ad Appropriation (Box 255)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.641 Direct Mail/Direct Response (Box 255)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.643 Outdoor Advertising (Box 255)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.65 Cinema Advertising (Box 255)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.526 Copy Testing (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.53 Advertising Art (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.6 Media (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.601 International Media (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.61 Media Selection (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.617 Media Research (Box 361)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.221 Newspapers and Comics (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.61 Media Selection (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.617 Media Research (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.62 Press (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.6221 Magazines (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.915 Media Rates (Box 370)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.65 Cinema Advertising (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.66 Radio--Audience and Research (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67 Commercial Television and TV Companies (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67003 Television Advertising Expenditure and Revenue (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.6706 Independent Broadcasting Authority (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67063 Breakfast Television (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67065 ITV (Independent Television) Companies (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67072 Television Audience Research (Box 326)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.67072 TV Audience Research (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.672 Television Programmes (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.6721 Television Commercials (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.6722 Animals in Advertising (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.7 Merchandising General (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.701 Character Merchandising (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.702 Brand Diversification (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.72 Sales Promotion (Box 269)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.726 Coupon Offers (Box 262A)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.734 Pricing (Box 262A)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.780037 Packaging Regulations (Box 262A)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.727 Gift Buying (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.76 Point of Sale (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.78 Packaging (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.781 Packaging--Drinks (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 659.7815 Packaging--Aerosols (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.1 Non-Alcoholic Drinks--General (Box 262)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.14 Tea (Box 388)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.16 Fruit Juices (Box 388)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.17 Soft Drinks (Box 388)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.18 Carbonated Soft Drinks (Box 388)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.22 Drinks (Box 388)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.3 Beer and Breweries (Box 358)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.31 Take-Home Beer (Cans, Bottles) (Box 358)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.32 Lager (Box 358)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.33 Ale (Box 358)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.4 Cider and Perry (Box 358)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.5 Wine (Box 302)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.51 Cooler Drinks (Box 302)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.6 Fortified Wines (Box 302)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.7 Champagne (Box 302)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.81 Whiskey (Box 302)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.8 Spirits (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.82 Gin (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.83 Rum (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.84 Brandy (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.85 Vodka (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.86 Liqueurs (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 663.9 Aperatifs and Vermouth (Box 9)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.00037 Food Laws (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.003 Food Prices (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.03 Organic Foods (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.0382 Food Production (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.04 Synthetic Foods (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.09 Food Franchising/Fast Food (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.091 Ethnic Food (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.095 Take-Away (Box 241)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664 Delicatessen (Box 301)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664 Food and Food Industry (Box 301)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.00037 Food Laws (Box 301)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.1 Confectionery (Box 258)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.14 Chocolate Confectionery (Box 258)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.14 Chocolate (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.15 Chewing Gum (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.2 Flour and Flour Mills (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.22 Baking Industry and Bakers (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.23 Bread (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.24 Pasta and Rice (Box 299)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.25 Food--Biscuits (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.262 Food--Cakes (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.27 Food--Puddings and Desserts (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.28 Food--Breakfast Cereals (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.29 Food--Ready Mixes (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.3 Food--Preservatives (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.35 Food--Canned (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.634 Food--Canned Fruit (Box 375)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.35.641 Canned Meat (Box 267)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.36 Pre-Packaged Foods (Box 267)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.5 Frozen Food (Box 267)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.55 Ice Cream (Box 267)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.55 Ice Cream (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.6 Preserves (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.62 Jam (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.63 Marmelade (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.65 Table Jellies (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.658 Food Marketing/Packaging (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.7 Condiments (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.71 Herbs (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.72 Spices (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.74 Salt (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.79 Salad Cream (Box 314)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.76 Pickles and Sauces (Box 320)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.8 Soups (Box 320)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.84 Meat and Fish Paste (Box 320)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.87 Baby Food and Care (Box 320)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.9 Crisps and Snacks (Box 320)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.8851 Cereal Bars (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 664.9 Crisps and Snacks (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 665.2 Animal Oils and Fats (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 665.3 Vegetable Oils and Fats (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 665.5 Oil Industry (Food) (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.1 Detergents and Washing Products (Box 313)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.1 Detergents and Washing Powders (Box 266)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.2 Dishwashing Liquids (Box 266)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.3 Toiletries and Cosmetics (Box 266)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.4 Soap (Box 266)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.5 Facial Cosmetics (Box 266)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.64 Oral Hygiene (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.7 Hair Preparations (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.71 Shampoos (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.8 Shaving Products (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.81 Men's Toiletries (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.85 Depilatories (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.9 Skin Care Products (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.92 Suntan Lotions (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.93 Deodorants (Box 253)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.93 Deodorants (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 668.95 Perfumes (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.6 Tobacco (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.62 Cigarettes (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.63 Cigars (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.64 Snuff (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.65 Smoker Requisites (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.651 Pipes (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.652 Matches (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.653 Lighters (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 679.66 Smoking and Health (Box 252)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.151 Electronics Industry (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1512 Information Technology (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1514 Semiconductors and Microchips (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1515 Computers (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1515A Computer Companies (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1515B Computer Peripherals (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1516 Personal Computers (Box 273)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1517 Computer Retailing (Box 271)
    - Knowledge Centre Subject Files: 681.1518 Computer Software (Box 271)